Hi
[Music]
I'm Singles
Nau this is one extraordinary Joni we
should be good and professional
for customers Vision and cloud value
ikonight Awards Diane JNE on FB
What if I change my cellphone so the
effect is man
success is energy to be successful full of
energy and great success requires
great energy
[Music]
the scene thirty Seven
of
well-known below
Hi Effendi the car is a
single application that contains all
the applications needed by all of us who
are in the official fare agency there has been a collaboration
between fade Life Indonesia and you
meatballs here we collaborate with fwd
Life and we again provide a breakthrough
to the Indonesian people to
change their thinking about
insurance for that Bawuk starting today
Ladies and Gentlemen Let's start our success
together with fwd Life Indonesia so
we have more than 10 Rider syakroni
yes it would be a shame if we do not
penetrate the
hadiths that we have use
this opportunity to make us the
most successful Regency fwd
in Indonesia fwd Life will
stop
10mb meaning first where will we go
To Orlando's
Hi  The effect is getting more and more solid with the event
we just watched, even more solid,
even more solid and even more solid, I
invite all of you to
join FWD, free your steps
[Music]